music-jobs.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy | UK Music Jobs

We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. It describes how we treat personal information when you use our services and how you can manage the communication we have with you.

## Personal information

You need register with us in order to use our services. We ask for some personal information when you register, including your alternate contact information and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. This allows you to access many of our services that require registration. We store, process and maintain this information in order to provide the service to you.

When you use our services our servers automatically record certain information about your usage. Similar to other web services, we record information such as account activity, data displayed or clicked on; and other log information.

## Uses

Our administrative staff maintain and process your contact details and the content of your profile to provide the service to you and to improve our services. 

We will send you, as necessary from time to time, information related to administration of your profile or the services you have registered to receive.

In addition you can chose to opt in or out of other communication from us which currently includes job alerts, information about your profile viewings and a weekly news digest. This information may be subject to change, in which case you will be notified and will have the option to opt in or out of receiving it. 

You may chose to whether or not you wish to receive information from third parties, the content of which will be approved by us. You may edit your choice at any time using your profile settings.

This site uses cookies as described in the [Cookie Policy](http://www.media-match.com/uk/music/cookies.php)

## Information sharing and onward transfer

We will not sell, rent or otherwise share your personal information with any third parties without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law.

In addition to this you can chose which groups of people have access to your contact details and to the content of your profile. You can change your privacy settings at any time by editing your profile settings. 

## Your choices

You may change your choices at any time through your profile settings.

You may cancel the service and unsubscribe at any time you like using the cancel button in your profile settings.

If you have any queries or concerns you can email us at: [ uk-music@media-match.com](mailto:uk-music@media-match.com "Contact Us!").
